Guide to the C&U Poster Advertising Company Records, 1896-2004 and undated RL.11125
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
C&U Poster Advertising Company Records, 1896-2004 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
C&U Poster Advertising Company.
RL.11125
72.0 Linear Feet
Outdoor advertising company founded in 1912 in the Champaign-Urbana, Illinois environs.
Arrangement
Arranged into 12 series: General Files; Kip Pope Papers; Legal Files; Meetings; Organizations; Press and Publicity; Printed Material; Slides and Photographic Materials; Ledgers and Minute Books; Oversize Materials; Audiovisual Materials; Digital Materials. Where possible original folder titles have been retained.
Biographical / Historical
Founded 1912 as the A.E. Price Company, but changed name to Champaign-Urbana Poster Co. Frederick H. Gillingham and Charles Loeb acquired the company in the 1920s, and Gillingham became sole owner around 1945. Company transfered to Gillingham's daughter Barbara, whose husband Bob Pope ran the company until 1980. In 1984 Bob and Barbara's son Kip Pope acquired majority ownership and ran the company until 2001, when it was acquired by Adams Outdoor.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
However, original audiovisual and digital materials are closed until use copies can be produced.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The C&U Poster Advertising Company Records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as gift in 2004 and 2009.
Related Materials
Related materials may be found in the following Hartman Center collections: Outdoor Advertising Association of America Archives; Naegele Outdoor Records; Ohio Outdoor Advertising Corporation Records.
Collection Overview
Collection spans 1896-2004 and includes photographs, slides, correspondence, ledgers and minute books, administrative and financial records, research reports and other printed materials. Legal materials include court proceedings, depositions, as well as published collections of local, state and federal legislation, zoning ordinances and court rulings. Organizations represented include the Hoopeston Advertising Company, Outdoor Advertising Association of America, Outdoor Advertising Association of Illinois. Included are the papers of Kip Pope, owner and manager of the company 1984-2001. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Advertising, Outdoor -- History; Advertising, Outdoor -- United States; Advertising, Outdoor -- Law and legislation; Outdoor Advertising Association of America -- Membership; Illinois -- History; Advertising agencies -- Illinois; C&U Poster Advertising Company.
- General Files, 1915-2000 and undated; 1
  - General A-C, 1929-2000 and undated; 1
    - Agreement with OAI, 1963 (Box 1)
    - Allenton removed billboards, 1986-1988 (Box 1)
    - Amortization, 1984-1992 (Box 1)
    - Artwork for publications, 1998 (Box 1)
    - Billboards sold vs. available, 1985-2000 (Box 1)
    - Building Wrap, undated (Box 1)
    - Capital stock tax returns, 1933-1965 (Box 1)
    - Champaign Chamber of Commerce certificate, 1929 (Box 1)
    - Champaign permits, 1947-1973 (Box 1)
    - Contract for outdoor advertising, 1946-1972; 4 folders (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1948-2000 and undated; 2
    - A-C alphabetical, 1966-1969; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Champaign County Bank and Trust, undated (Box 2)
    - D alphabetical, 1967-1970 (Box 2)
    - D'Arcy MacManus & Masius, 1973-1974 (Box 2)
    - Department of Public Works and Buildings, 1967-1972 (Box 2)
    - E-G alphabetical, 1967-1973 (Box 2)
    - General Outdoor, 1950 (Box 2)
    - Group letters, 1956-1977 (Box 2)
    - H alphabetical, 1967-1969 (Box 2)
    - Herrin Signs, undated (Box 2)
    - I alphabetical, 1967-1968 (Box 2)
    - Illinois Power Company, 1970-1973 (Box 2)
    - Independents, undated (Box 2)
    - J alphabetical, 1967-1971 (Box 2)
    - Jefferson Outdoor Sales, 1973-1974 (Box 2)
    - K alphabetical, 1966-1973 (Box 2)
    - KSH Chemical, 1975-1977 (Box 2)
    - L alphabetical, 1966-1973 (Box 2)
    - Letters of complaint, 1989-1993 (Box 2)
    - Letters positive used in lawsuit, 1957-1976 (Box 2)
    - Letters to cities, 1986 (Box 3)
    - Letters to editor, Christian Science Monitor, 1972 (Box 3)
    - M alphabetical, 1966-1973 (Box 3)
    - Marsters Sign Co., 1969 (Box 3)
    - Meadow Gold/Kemper, 1969 (Box 3)
    - N alphabetical, 1966-1974 (Box 3)
    - National Council on Crime, undated (Box 3)
    - Negative letters, 1986 (Box 3)
    - O alphabetical, 1966-1975 (Box 3)
    - OAA Convention, 1967 (Box 3)
    - OAAI, 1968 (Box 3)
    - P alphabetical, 1968-1975 (Box 3)
    - Paradise Inn, 1964-1969 (Box 3)
    - Political, 1977 (Box 3)
    - Proposals, 1968-1975 (Box 3)
    - Public relations outgoing, 1986-1987 (Box 3)
    - R alphabetical, 1968-1974 (Box 3)
    - Rate sheets, 1969 (Box 3)
    - Riegel Truck, 1971-1974 (Box 4)
    - S alphabetical, 1968-1975 (Box 4)
    - Standard Oil, 1968-1969 (Box 4)
    - T alphabetical, 1967-1977 (Box 4)
    - Techniprint, 1971 (Box 4)
    - Testimonials, 1948-2000; 3 folders (Box 4)
    - Thank you letters, 1986-1998 (Box 4)
    - Thank you letters, 1986-1998 (Box 5)
    - Tiffin, 1968-1971 (Box 5)
    - U-Z alphabetical, 1967-1972; 4 folders (Box 5)
  - General D-Z, 1915-2000 and undated; 3
    - Danville, Illinois, 1964-1967 (Box 5)
    - Defensive driving, undated (Box 5)
    - Design sheets, 1975-1978; 4 folders (Box 5)
    - Employee uniform badges, undated (Box 5)
    - F.H. Gillingham, 1942-1951 (Box 6)
    - FS Buildings billboard design, circa 1985 (Box 6)
    - HAL/Cyberfest, 1997 (Box 6)
    - Hazard communications, 1987 (Box 6)
    - Hoopeston Poster Advertising, 1915-1989; 4 folders (Box 6)
    - Income/Tax, 1941-1985; 4 folders (Box 6)
    - Invoices, 1967-1968 (Box 6)
    - Kux Mfg.--Suggested Truck and Van Marking (work vehicles), undated (Box 6)
    - Leases and permits, 1949-2000; 5 folders (Box 7)
    - Letterhead, undated (Box 7)
    - Location book, 1997 (Box 7)
    - Loewy trim, 1946-1995 (Box 7)
    - Miscellaneous documents, 1947-1981; 3 folders (Box 7)
    - Mission statement, undated (Box 8)
    - Old advertisements removed, 1957-1984 (Box 8)
    - Old documents (A.E. Price, Gill, Loeb, etc.), 1915-1947 (Box 8)
    - Personal property taxes, 1960-1978 (Box 8)
    - Plant records, 1957-1958 (Box 8)
    - Posting charts/lists/reports, 1937-1997; 5 folders (Box 8)
    - Presentation to Urbana Planning Commission, 1969 (Box 8)
    - Questionnaire, 1997 (Box 8)
    - Rate cards, 1970-1990 (Box 8)
    - Research papers about C&U Poster, 1967-1979 (Box 8)
    - S. Neil Street widening project, 1988-1995; 3 folders (Box 8)
    - State acquisitions, 1974 (Box 9)
    - Statement of capacity, 1974 (Box 9)
    - Stock returns, 1936-1977; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Stockholders meeting, 1940-1946 (Box 9)
    - Top 10 advertisers, 1986-1997 (Box 9)
    - Unemployment insurance, 1960s (Box 9)
    - Urbana sign permits, 1967-1972 (Box 9)
    - Wage reports, 1950s (Box 9)
    - Wolohan Lumber, 1968-1971 (Box 9)
    - Zoning, 1970 (Box 9)
    - Zoning map of Champaign, 1986 (Box 9)
- Kip Pope Papers, 1924-2002 and undated; 2
  - General Files, 1924-2002 and undated; 4
    - A New Way to Buy Painted Outdoor Advertising (POAA), 1924 (Box 10)
    - Ad Club speech--History of C&U Poster, 2001 (Box 10)
    - Advertising management, 1994 (Box 10)
    - Aesthetics and Public Relations (Outdoor Advertising Magazine article), 1995; 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Amortization article, undated; 4 folders (Box 10)
    - APA Illinois State Conference, 2001 (Box 10)
    - Appearances: Billboards and Landscaping (Outdoor Advertising Magazine article), 1996 (Box 10)
    - Appearances: Unipoles and Aesthetics (Outdoor Advertising Magazine article), 1996 (Box 11)
    - Billboard aesthetics, 2002 (Box 11)
    - Binder, Illinois Municipal League, undated (Box 11)
    - C&U Poster aesthetics, undated (Box 11)
    - Columns/Treadway Industries, 2000 (Box 11)
    - Community relations and awareness, 1991 (Box 11)
    - Design rules, 1991-1994 (Box 11)
    - Everybody Wants to Get into Public Relations! (Anheuser-Busch), undated (Box 11)
    - Exchange between F.H. Gillingham (C&U), Harold Eves (OAAA), W.F. Greeley (Greeley & Sons), 1949-1960 (Box 11)
    - Exciting opportunities, 1999 (Box 11)
    - Federal and State Control of Outdoor Advertising along the Highways (B706 paper for Nicholas White), undated (Box 11)
    - Florida OAA speech, 2001; 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Geometric shape enclosure, undated (Box 11)
    - Illinois Municipal League presentation, 1999 (Box 11)
    - John Gann articles, 1999-2001 (Box 11)
    - Letter to Rep. Thomas W. Ewing, 1990-1992 (Box 12)
    - Letter to Rep. Tim Johnson and Helen Satterthwaite, 1990 (Box 12)
    - MBA Forum, 1994 (Box 12)
    - Media planning, 1998 (Box 12)
    - Miscellaneous documents, 1980-2002 (Box 12)
    - Murals, undated (Box 12)
    - Neil Street improvements, 1996 (Box 12)
    - OAAA, 1969-1994; 2 folders (Box 12)
    - OAAA Operations Seminar, 1996 (Box 12)
    - OAAI safety poster campaign, 1950 (Box 12)
    - OAI Western Division assignment list, 1963 (Box 12)
    - Organization Authorities and Responsibilities (OAAA), undated (Box 12)
    - Outdoor Advertising Inc. (OAI), 1931-1959 (Box 12)
    - Outdoor advertising in France, 1988; 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Overcoming obstacles, 2000 (Box 12)
    - Plan and Purpose of the OAAA, circa 1969 (Box 12)
    - Promotional flyer: A Masterpiece, undated (Box 12)
    - Regulating Outdoor Advertising, 2000 (Box 12)
    - Report of activities, 1989-1997; 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Roadside Problem in California (Foster & Kleiser), 1940 (Box 12)
    - Seabrook, undated (Box 12)
    - Speeches and publications, 2000 (Box 12)
    - TAB--Circulation Characteristics of Poster Advertising Plants, 1937 (Box 12)
    - Updates, 2000 (Box 12)
- Legal Files, 1905-2002 and undated; 3
  - General Files, 1912-2002 and undated; 5
    - Agreement Illinois/FHWA, 1977 (Box 13)
    - Arbors Mobile Home Park, 1980 (Box 13)
    - Bob O'Dell, 1980-1982 (Box 13)
    - C, 1977 (Box 13)
    - Early corporate documents, 1912-1962 (Box 13)
    - Executive Order 12630 and Attorney General guidelines, 1988 (Box 13)
    - FHWA letters, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
    - Forrest Clark Ramada Inn, 1969-1973 (Box 13)
    - Fred Conrad, 1988 (Box 13)
    - General licenses--Urbana, 1930-1969 (Box 13)
    - General photocopies, 1947-1962 (Box 13)
    - HACA (Highway Advertising Control Act), 1983; 2 folders (Box 13)
    - HB-3680, 1971 (Box 13)
    - HBA (Highway Beautification Act)legislative history, 1978 (Box 13)
    - HR-713, undated (Box 14)
    - Highway Advertising Control Act, 1971 (Box 14)
    - Hirschfield litigation, 1958-1962 (Box 14)
    - Hopkins Pontiac/Lincoln-Mercury, 1983 (Box 14)
    - Illinois Bell, 1979-1983 (Box 14)
    - Illinois Dept. of Transportation, 1966-1983; 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Katsinas, 1986 (Box 14)
    - Kirby vs. Welker, 1975 (Box 14)
    - Kroger, 1980 (Box 14)
    - Larry Kirby vs. Champaign Signs, 1975 (Box 14)
    - Legal cases, 1978-1991 (Box 14)
    - Legislative history of HBA, 1958-1978; 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Letters regarding sign regulation, 1967-1971 (Box 15)
    - Lucas vs. South Carolina Coastal Council, 1992 (Box 15)
    - Mark Ulmer, 1987-1997; 3 folders (Box 15)
    - Marked transparencies of HACA, undated (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous documents, 1977-1999; 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Moratorium-Sign Ordinance--C, 2000-2001 (Box 15)
    - Moratorium-Sign Ordinance--Cantilever, undated (Box 16)
    - Moratorium-Sign Ordinance--Champaign Downtown Association, 2001 (Box 16)
    - Moratorium-Sign Ordinance--Champaign Sign Ordinance, undated (Box 16)
    - Moratorium-Sign Ordinance--Ch. 1 from general notebook, 2001 (Box 16)
    - Moratorium-Sign Ordinance--CMI Council, 2000 (Box 16)
    - Moratorium-Sign Ordinance--Florida pictures, undated (Box 16)
    - Moratorium-Sign Ordinance--Local newspaper articles, 2000-2001 (Box 16)
    - Moratorium-Sign Ordinance--Miscellaneous, 1985-2001; 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Moratorium-Sign Ordinance--OAAA, 2000 (Box 16)
    - Moratorium-Sign Ordinance--OASS Task Force, 2001; 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Moratorium-Sign Ordinance--Proposed point system, undated (Box 16)
    - Moratorium-Sign Ordinance--Roof projection, undated (Box 16)
    - Moratorium-Sign Ordinance--Scenic America, 2000 (Box 16)
    - Moratorium-Sign Ordinance--Studies and research, 2000 (Box 17)
    - Moratorium-Sign Ordinance--Talking points, 1992 (Box 17)
    - Moratorium-Sign Ordinance--Urbana OASS ordinance, 2001-2002 (Box 17)
    - Moratorium-Sign Ordinance--Urbana sign ordinance, undated (Box 17)
    - Newspaper articles on sign ordinance, 1967-1971 (Box 17)
    - OAAA--Dolan vs. City of Tigard, 1994 (Box 17)
    - OAAI--Almota right to compensation, 1976-1993 (Box 17)
    - Paul's Restaurant, 1984-1985 (Box 17)
    - Pope Welker income, 1973 (Box 17)
    - Proposed sign ordinances, 1969-1971; 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Redwood Inn, 1981 (Box 18)
    - Regional Plan Commission Ordinance, 1967 (Box 18)
    - Rudy Frasca, 1992 (Box 18)
    - Sign ordinances, 1969 (Box 18)
    - Sister Mary Long, 1986 (Box 18)
    - SR-709, 1965 (Box 18)
    - Starr Imports, 1983-1992 (Box 18)
    - State legislative history of HACA, 1965-1979 (Box 18)
    - Tables, HBA/HACA, undated (Box 18)
    - Ted Christman, 1979 (Box 18)
    - The Bar, 1984 (Box 18)
    - Tobacco and alcohol, 1988-1990 (Box 18)
    - Trans World Express, 1994 (Box 18)
    - Vac-Man, 1986 (Box 18)
    - Valuation of OASS/GRM, 1992 (Box 19)
    - Vermont vs. Brinegar, S. Dakota opinion, 1977 (Box 19)
    - Vince's Auto Repair, 1981 (Box 19)
    - Vriner's Confectionary, 1986 (Box 19)
    - Wendco, 1980 (Box 19)
    - White Hen Pantry, 1980-1981 (Box 19)
    - White Horse Inn, 1985 (Box 19)
    - Willie's Pizza, 1980-1983 (Box 19)
  - C&U Poster vs. Champaign-Urbana, 1905-2001 and undated; 6
    - 1988 hearing, 3 folders (Box 20)
    - Accident report summary, 1977-1980 (Box 20)
    - Amended zoning ordinance, 1965 (Box 20)
    - Anatomy of a lawsuit notes, undated (Box 20)
    - Ann Arbor, 1967-1982 (Box 20)
    - Arkansas and Missouri cases, 1973 (Box 20)
    - ASPO (American Society of Planning Officials) Green Book, 1951-1972 (Box 20)
    - Beesley court cases, 1975 (Box 20)
    - Big Ten cities sign ordinances, 1981-1982 (Box 20)
    - Big Ten cities sign ordinances, 1981-1982 (Box 21)
    - Bill of particulars, 1975 (Box 21)
    - Billboard permits Champaign, 1950-1974 (Box 21)
    - Billboards purposes and uniqueness etc., undated (Box 21)
    - Billboards effect on value of surrounding properties, undated (Box 21)
    - BOCA Basic Building Code, 1981 (Box 21)
    - Brochures and articles on regulation of outdoor advertising, 1957-1972; 3 folders (Box 21)
    - Building and fire safety codes, 1982 (Box 22)
    - Building permits Champaign, 1947-1973 (Box 22)
    - Businesses (including United Way) using outdoor advertising, undated (Box 22)
    - C&U Poster, 1983-1988 (Box 22)
    - C&U Poster--appeal file, 1980-1984 (Box 22)
    - C&U Poster--law clerks, 1980-1983 (Box 22)
    - C&U Poster--Pleadings post-trial, 1984 (Box 22)
    - C&U Poster--Sec. 1988 file, 2 folders (Box 22)
    - C&U Poster--Sign ordinances, 1972-1977; 2 folders (Box 22)
    - C&U Poster--Sign ordinances, 1975-1976 (Box 23)
    - C&U Poster--Urbana, 1971-1982; 2 folders (Box 23)
    - Certificates, 1982 (Box 23)
    - Champaign--Case files, 1974-1982 (Box 23)
    - Champaign--City Code, 1964 (Box 23)
    - Champaign--HACA permits, 1972 (Box 23)
    - Champaign--Zoning ordinances, 1980 (Box 23)
    - City Councils, 1976-1977 (Box 23)
    - City of Urbana, 1977-1979 (Box 23)
    - Closing arguments, 1983 (Box 23)
    - Colorado and South Dakota cases, 1973 (Box 23)
    - Combined Communications Corporation (CCC) vs. Denver, 1970-1980 (Box 23)
    - Combined Communications Corporation (CCC) vs. Denver, 1970-1980; 8 folders (Box 24)
    - Combined Communications Corporation (CCC) vs. Denver, 1975; 8 folders (Box 25)
    - Comprehensive Sign Ordinance, 1975 (Box 25)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1999; 3 folders (Box 26)
    - Council Bill 77-203 (Special Events Signs) and 75-09, 1975 (Box 26)
    - Court hearings and meetings with attorneys, 1977-1982 (Box 26)
    - Court memorandum opinion, 1983; 2 folders (Box 26)
    - Depositions, undated (Box 26)
    - Digest of Legal Decisions Relating to Outdoor Advertising (OAAA), 1970; 5 folders (Box 27)
    - Discovery, 1983 (Box 27)
    - Discovery--Urbana Planning Commission, 1971 (Box 28)
    - Discovery depositions, 1970-1983; 6 folders (Box 28)
    - Discovery depositions, 1970-1983; 8 folders (Box 29)
    - Discovery outline, undated (Box 29)
    - Dolson vs. Rantoul, 1977-1979; 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Enft. Officials, 1982 and undated (Box 30)
    - Eminent domain, undated (Box 30)
    - Evidence depositions, 1982-1983; 3 folders (Box 30)
    - Exhibit A-B, undated; 3 folders (Box 30)
    - Exhibit C-E, undated; 4 folders (Box 31)
    - Expenses, 1988 (Box 31)
    - Fair Labor Standards Act, 1958 (Box 31)
    - Federal, undated (Box 31)
    - Final hearing, 1983 (Box 31)
    - Final order, 1982 (Box 31)
    - Florida and California cases, 1973 (Box 31)
    - Future ordinances, 2001 (Box 31)
    - Group exhibits, undated (Box 32)
    - Hearing transcript, 1982 (Box 32)
    - Illinois, 1973-1974 (Box 32)
    - Indiana-Burns St., 1971 (Box 32)
    - Inverse condemnation, 1972-1980 (Box 32)
    - J. Stannard Baker (expert witness), 1983 (Box 32)
    - La Mesa case, 1977 (Box 32)
    - Law clerk memos and notes, 1982-1983; 2 folders (Box 32)
    - Leases and licenses--Champaign, 1952-1981 (Box 32)
    - Legislative history Comprehensive Sign Ordinance, 1969-1977 (Box 32)
    - Legislative history Comprehensive Sign Ordinance, 1969-1977 (Box 33)
    - M-N alphabetical, 1982 (Box 33)
    - Market Value Appraisal, 1982 (Box 33)
    - Maryland, Michigan and general United States cases, 1963-1973 (Box 33)
    - Memoranda, 1972-1982; 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Mental health, undated (Box 33)
    - Metromedia vs. Des Plaines, 1975 (Box 33)
    - Metromedia vs. San Diego, 1975-1980; 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Metromedia vs. San Diego, 1976-1982; 10 folders (Box 34)
    - Metromedia vs. San Diego, 1975-1985; 11 folders (Box 35)
    - Metromedia vs. San Diego, 1980-1981; 3 folders (Box 36)
    - Miscellaneous exhibits at trial, undated (Box 36)
    - Miscellaneous law for trial--Articles on billboards and zoning, 1951-1977 (Box 36)
    - Miscellaneous law for trial--Articles on zoning, fees, damage, aesthetics, 1972-1988 (Box 36)
    - Miscellaneous law for trial--City Attorney, legislation, penalties, 1905-1916 (Box 36)
    - Miscellaneous law for trial--Conspiracy, notices, injunctions, 1975-1979 (Box 36)
    - Miscellaneous law for trial--Equal protection, 1917-1943 (Box 36)
    - Miscellaneous law for trial--Free speech, 1968-1978 (Box 36)
    - Miscellaneous law for trial--Home rule, 1970-1979 (Box 36)
    - Miscellaneous law for trial--Mandamus, tort immunity, 1973-1983 (Box 36)
    - Miscellaneous law for trial--Necessity to exhaust administrative remedies, 1957-1975 (Box 36)
    - Miscellaneous law for trial--Property law, 1985 (Box 36)
    - Miscellaneous law for trial--Publication and notice requirements, 1961-1975 (Box 36)
    - Miscellaneous law for trial--Unauthorized delegation of authority, 1961-1978 (Box 37)
    - Miscellaneous law for trial--Unauthorized practice of law and zoning, 1962-1978 (Box 37)
    - Miscellaneous law for trial--Vested routes and estoppel, 1963-1970 (Box 37)
    - Miscellaneous research, undated (Box 37)
    - Model ordinances, 1965 and undated (Box 37)
    - Moratorium ordinance, 1974 (Box 37)
    - New ordinances--Champaign, 1983-1984 (Box 37)
    - New York and Vermont cases, 1967-1973 (Box 37)
    - Newspaper articles on sign ordinance decision, 1976-1985 (Box 37)
    - Notes taken at trial by law clerk, undated; 2 folders (Box 37)
    - Old papers from Stuart Mamer's file, 1944-1965 (Box 37)
    - Ordinance 1018, 1965-1970 (Box 37)
    - Oregon decision, 1982 (Box 38)
    - Other cities' ordinances, 1980; 3 folders (Box 38)
    - Plaintiff exhibit photographs, undated (Box 38)
    - Planners--Aesthetics, undated (Box 38)
    - Proposed Findings of Facts and Conclusions of Law, 1982 (Box 38)
    - Recodified zoning ordinance, 1980 (Box 38)
    - Regional Planning Commission, 1976-1978 (Box 38)
    - Settlement agreement, 1984-1995; 4 folders (Box 39)
    - Settlement agreement--Champaign, 1983-1989; 3 folders (Box 39)
    - Settlement agreement--Urbana, 1984-1985; 2 folders (Box 39)
    - Settlement agreement--Urbana, 1985; 3 folders (Box 40)
    - Site leases--Urbana, 1976 (Box 40)
    - Southern California Research Foundation, 1973 (Box 40)
    - Statutes and ordinances, 1976 and undated (Box 40)
    - Summary judgment, 1982 and undated (Box 40)
    - Trial and witness files, 1980-1983; 9 folders (Box 40)
    - Trial and witness files, 1980-1983; 6 folders (Box 41)
    - Trial and witness files, 1980-1983; 11 folders (Box 42)
    - Trial and witness files, 1983 (Box 43)
    - Trial brief, 1957-1983; 5 folders (Box 43)
    - Trial commencement, 1982; 2 folders (Box 43)
    - Trial exhibits, 1973-1982 (Box 43)
    - Trial notes, 1965-1983; 6 folders (Box 44)
    - Urban Ordinance Kit, undated; 2 folders (Box 44)
    - Urban Ordinance Kit, undated; 2 folders (Box 45)
    - Urbana--Building permits, 1958-1971 (Box 45)
    - Urbana--HACA permits, 1972 (Box 45)
    - Urbana--Leases and licenses, 1960-1982 (Box 45)
    - Urbana--Ordinance case files, 1968-1971 (Box 45)
    - Urbana--Sign Ordinance, 1967-1971; 3 folders (Box 45)
    - Urbana--Zoning, 1970-1981; 2 folders (Box 46)
    - Various cases, 1960-1976 (Box 46)
    - Virginia State Board of Pharmacy, 1975-1976 (Box 46)
    - Wagner, Starmos (First Amendment case), 1970-1982 (Box 46)
    - Zoning Ordinance of Champaign, 1965-1972 (Box 46)
- Meetings, 1973-2000; 4
  - General Files, 1973-2000; 7
    - Billboard seminar--Chicago, 1973 (Box 46)
    - Innovation Workshop, 1991; 2 folders (Box 46)
    - International Outdoor Advertising Conference--South Africa, 1999; 2 folders (Box 46)
    - Kip Pope OAAA Hall of Fame, 1997 (Box 47)
    - Managing Multiple Priorities, 1987 (Box 47)
    - Miscellaneous, 1986-1988 (Box 47)
    - OAAA Convention, 1990-1998; 7 folders (Box 47)
    - OAAA Convention, 1999; 3 folders (Reel 48)
    - OAAA Executive Committee, 1995-1997; 2 folders (Reel 48)
    - OAAA/FOARE meeting, 1999 (Reel 48)
    - OAAA Grassroots/Scenic Byways, 1994 (Reel 48)
    - OAAA Legal Forum, 1986-1994; 2 folders (Reel 48)
    - OAAA Legal Seminar, 1989-1996; 3 folders (Reel 48)
    - OAAA Legislative Committee, 1999 (Reel 48)
    - OAAA Legislative Conference, 2000 (Box 49)
    - OAAA Legislative Fly-In, 1995 (Box 49)
    - OAAA Lobby Seminar, 1990 (Box 49)
    - OAAA Operations Seminar, 1988-1996; 4 folders (Box 49)
    - OAAA Region III, 1994 (Box 49)
    - OAAA Seminar--O'Hare (James Claus), 1975 (Box 49)
    - OAAA Winter Conference, 1994 (Box 49)
    - OAAA Winter Public Affairs Conference, 1996 (Box 50)
    - Tri-State Sales Conference, 1991 (Box 50)
    - Valuation analysis seminar (Ruppert & Ruppert), circa 1991 (Box 50)
    - World Outdoor Advertising Congress (Paris), 1986; 2 folders (Box 50)